[{"id": 1782, "question": "The father's role in the family is important. One researcher says babies cared for by their fathers have greater cognitive development at one year of age than babies not cared for by their fathers. Another expert reports that by spending time with their pre-school children, fathers can help to develop children's language ability. Researchers also point out that for school-age children, fathers are one link with the outside world. Fathers who value education have children who do better in school than those children whose fathers don't value education. What's more, fathers who spend quality time with their children may give their children happy memories which may last a lifetime. While each father is a unique person who educates children in his own style, good fathers have something in commo...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _   .", "options": ["how to be a qualified father", "the growth and development of both fathers and children", "the father's role in the growth and development of children", "the changing of the father's role in modern society"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 482, "question": "I recently turned fifty, which is young for a tree, midlife for an elephant, and ancient for a sportsman. Fifty is a nice number for the states in the US or for a national speed limit but it is not a number that I was prepared to have hung on me. Fifty is supposed to be my father's age, but now I am stuck with this number and everything it means. A few days ago, a friend tried to cheer me up by saying, \" Fifty is what forty used to be.\" He had made an inspirational point, Am I over the hill?People keep telling me that the hill has been moved, and I keep telling them that he high-jump bar has dropped from the six feet I once easily cleared to the four feet that is impossible for me now. \" Your are not getting older, you are getting better.\" says Dr. Joyce Brothers. This, however, is the kin...\n\nQ: When the author turned fifty, people around him    _   .", "options": ["tried to comfort him", "got inspiration with him", "were friendlier with him", "found him more talkative"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2984, "question": "Though the facts that too many people on earth and a too rapid increase in the number added each year are not in argument, we always begin the discussion of \"population as global issue\" with what most persons mean like this. It was quite right to compare demographic growth to \"a long, thin powder fuse that bums steadily and hesitatingly until it finally reaches the charge and explodes\". To understand the current situation, which is characterized by rapid increases in population, it is necessary to understand the history of population trends. Rapid growth is a comparatively recent phenomenon. Looking back at the 8,000 years of demographic history, we find that populations have been virtually stable or growing very slightly for most of human history. For most of our ancestors, life was hard,...\n\nQ: Which of the following demographic growth patterns is most similar to the long thin powder fuse?", "options": ["A slow growth for a long time and then a period of rapid, dramatic increase.", "Too many people on earth and a few rapid increases in the number added each year.", "A virtually stable or slightly decreasing period and then a sudden explosion of population.", "A long period when death rates exceed birthrates and then a short period with higher fertility and lower mortality."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2176, "question": "The modern Olympic Games, founded in 1896, began as contests between individuals, rather than among nations, with the hope of promoting world peace through sportsmanship. In the beginning, the games were open only to amateurs. An amateur is a person whose involvement in an activity---from sports to science or the arts---is purely for pleasure. Amateurs, whatever their contributions to a field, expect to receive no form of compensation ; professionals, in contrast, perform their work in order to earn a living. From the perspective of many athletes, however, the Olympic playing field has been far from level. Restricting the Olympics to amateurs has precluded the participation of many who could not afford to be unpaid. Countries have always desired to send their best athletes, not their wealt...\n\nQ: One might infer that   _  .", "options": ["developing Olympic-level skills in athletes is costly", "professional athletes are mostly interested in financial rewards", "amateurs does not expect to earn money at the sport that is played", "amateurs have a better attitude than professionals do"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 658, "question": "Want to know the dynamic pulse of China's economy? Get a glance of the most important business activities taking place here every day through Business Daily Update, a service offered by China Daily information via the World Wide Web. Placed under 10 categories, over 25 news items appear each day with the top three events highlighted all in English.Business Daily Update is just a few mouse clicks away. Subscribe to BDU for an annual fee of US $240.Email and fax services are also Available upon request. For more information, please contact Business Daily Update: Tel: (010)64941107, (010) 64924488 ext.2000; Fax: +86-10-64941125 Email: bdu@chinadaily.com.cn;URL:http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/bdu...\n\nQ: This advertisement will be very helpful to   _  .", "options": ["Chinese people", "foreign travelers", "foreign business people", "China Daily reporters"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1710, "question": "It's a warm summer afternoon. You're cooking up the catch of the day over a campfire. Suddenly, a few raindrops fall on your arms, and before you know it, the sky is opened up. Then you hear what sounds like thunder in the distance. What should you do? Your tent is close by and would offer shelter from the pouring rain. There's a campsite picnic shelter a few minutes down the path. And then you remember that your car is parked down the road. What's your safest choice to make sure you and your families are safe? It's a common question for many hikers and campers, especially when they are camping during summer months. Heading to your car is almost always the safest choice. Your tent and a picnic shelter will keep you dry, but they offer little or no protection against lightening. Your car, o...\n\nQ: The passage aims to tell us   _  .", "options": ["what's camping", "how to camp safely", "car camping is the safest way when camping", "how to survive a storm when camping"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2446, "question": "It's not easy to find a person with the qualities it takes to be a hero. I didn't really understand the meaning of the word \"hero\" until my third year in the college. If you saw her, you wouldn't think she really looks the part, but she is stronger than Superman could ever be. Her name is Sandra Keierleber. I first met her at volleyball tryouts , but didn't notice anything special at first. As the week passed, however, she showed she had more heart than anyone. She stood out because she never gave up, no matter what. Sandra isn't the tallest or the fastest --- in fact, this was her first time playing volleyball and it showed--- but that didn't stop her. She was always the first to arrive and the last to leave. By the end of tryouts she had found a place in everyone's heart. When the name l...\n\nQ: Why does the writer think of Sandra Keierleber as a true hero?", "options": ["She did very well at the tryouts.", "She asked for help from her teammates.", "She took part in the city matches.", "She worked hard and never gave up."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 459, "question": "High school announcements Do you have a high school announcement to make? Are you hosting a high school sports event or tournament? Are you looking for a coach? Let us know, and we'll share it with \"Tribune\" readers. August 21---- Sacred Heart is looking for two assistant baseball coaches immediately. Practices and games are held after school at 3:30 pm. Some experience in playing or coaching is preferred. If interested, e-mail Ron Schwartz at ramsad1@aol.com. August 7 ----- Loyola Academy will host its 12th Rambler Baseball Winter Workshop for students in fourth through eighth grades on Aug. 26. the early registration fee is $70 and registration at the door is $85. contact Loyola coach Bill San Hamel at 847-920-2523 to register early. July 17 ----- St. Patrick will host a Youth Holiday Ba...\n\nQ: If a fourth-grade girl wants to learn baseball, she may contact  _  .", "options": ["Ron Schwartz", "Mary Pat Connolly", "Kusinski", "Bill San Hamel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1743, "question": "\"Colour\" and \"color1\" , \"favourite\" and \"favorite\"\"- Have you ever wondered why Americans spell those words without a \"u\"? Is it because they are lazy? Of course not.In fact, the difference in spelling was created by Noah Webster(1758--1843) .He is a teacher who reformed English to make American identity stronger.Linguists celebrated his 250th birthday on October 16,2008.After the Revolutionary War(1775--1783) , Webster believed that Americans should have their own dictionary, rather than rely on British versions.He dropped the British \"u\" in some words.And he changed \"centre\" into \"center\" for children to learn English by spelling words more like they sounded. Webster wasn't shy about expressing his opinions.In defining preposterous (unreasonable) , he wrote: \"A Republican government in t...\n\nQ: When did Noah Webster probably begin his project of the dictionary?", "options": ["In 1758.", "In 1783.", "In 1800.", "In 1828."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1254, "question": "Sons who have fond childhood memories of their fathers are more likely to be emotionally stable in the face of day-to-day stresses, according to psychologists who studied hundreds of adults of all ages. \"As our study shows, fathers do play a unique and important role in the mental health of their children much later in life,\" psychology professor Melanie Mallers of California State University said. For this study, 912 adult men and women between the ages of 25 and 74 completed short daily telephone interviews about that day's experiences over an eight-day period. The interviews focused on the participants' psychological and emotional distress (i.e.whether they were nervous, sad, etc.) and if they had experienced any stressful events that day. The participants were also required to answer q...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE about the findings of the study?", "options": ["People with a good relationship with others suffered less distress.", "Men with a good mother-child relationship were more likely to be emotionally stable than women.", "Women were more skilled at getting along with their parents than men.", "People with good childhood relationships with their parents suffered less stress."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3112, "question": "Then comes July, and with it examinations, but these are soon finished and with them ends the school year. Boys and girls have nearly two months' holiday before them as they leave school by train and car to return home to their fathers and mothers. The summer holidays are the best part of the year for most children. The weather is usually good, so that one can spend most of one's time playing in the garden or, if one lives in the country, out in the woods and fields. Even if one lives in a big town, one can usually go to a park to play. The best place for a summer holiday, however, is the seaside. Some children are lucky enough to live near the sea, but for the others who do not, a week or two at one of the big seaside towns is something that they will talk about for the whole of the follo...\n\nQ: After the examination, pupils leave for home  _", "options": ["by train only", "by air", "by bike", "by either train or car"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 742, "question": "When I was 13, my bedroom walls were covered with posters of the Monkees and Beatles. I wrote fan letters and daydreamed about meeting the objects of my affections. I begged my parents to attend every rock concert and watch every TV show featuring my favorite celebrities; my friends and I discussed for hours all the things we would say and do when we met our favourite movie stars and pop singers. I drove my mother crazy ! But after a few years, my obsession stars faded as I matured and gained the confidence to socialize with \"real\" boys. In the 35 years since I was a teenager, celebrity worship has increased among teens due to the explosion of television celebrity gossip shows, and instant access to celebrity news on the Internet. It's no wonder that many teens are obsessed with stars when...\n\nQ: Parents should become concerned when their children  _  .", "options": ["talk a lot about celebrities with others", "put up celebrity posters in their bedrooms", "ask to go to their favourite star's concert", "desire a close personal relationship with their favorite star"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2367, "question": "All the oceans of the world will be dead in the future unless action is taken at once. How can this happen? We have already seen that people allow all sorts of waste products to flow into the sea. It is almost impossible to measure how much waste water and industrial waste in our oceans, but we can find out how much oil is poured into them legally and illegally. It is illegal to pour oil into the sea close to the shore, but when a ship is many miles out to sea, there are no such rules. Scientists have different ideas as to the amount of oil putting into the sea, but the lowest figure for oil poured in European waters alone is nearly 200 000 tons every year. Some people say the figure could be ten times as high. It is not only our coasts that suffer from oil pollution. Many shell fish, for ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is illegal according to the passage?", "options": ["Pouring oil into the sea from land, especially when there is no other choice.", "Pouring oil at seaside.", "Allowing waste materials to flow into the waters.", "Going fishing when the water is polluted by oil."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3488, "question": "A family story is like a puzzle. Each family member leaves some clues. Family members come together because they have a common tie with one another, sharing a name and special traditions. Exploring family roots and sharing past memories ensure each tradition lives on. Ancestory.com has created customized \"Our Name is History\" books to give your family a look into your history by learning about your last name. By visiting _ , you can check if information is available for your last name. Ancestory.com researchers have collected more than 5 billion names from records such as passenger lists, immigration records and from birth, marriage and death records. The collected information is then used for each customized book. \"Our Name is History\" books are available for nearly 200,000 last names, ac...\n\nQ: What will mothers do if they get \"Our Name is History\" books?", "options": ["They may be inspired to talk about some special women they remember.", "They will collect information about their family roots.", "They will learn how great their ancestors are.", "They will share them with some other families."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2834, "question": "Almost everyone suffers from a headache sometimes.But some people suffer from repeated, frequent headaches. What is headache? What causes it? What can be done about a headache? What research is being done on headaches? The dictionary defines headache simply as \"a pain in the head.\" What most people mean by headache is a pain which lasts several minutes or hours.It covers the whole head, or one side of it, or perhaps the front or the back of the head.To add to the confusion about a definition, some people call tight feeling in the head a headache. A headache is important because it can be the first warning of a serious condition which probably could be controlled if discovered early.If a person removes the warning, day after day, with a pain-killer, he may pass the point of easy control. Th...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us  _  .", "options": ["the reason of headache", "headache and its effect", "everyone suffers from a headache", "a headache is a symptom of something serious"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3391, "question": "Little Tom down the street calls our dog \"The keep dog\".Zip is a sheep dog. But when Tom tries to say\" Seep\", it comes out \"keep\". And in a way Tom is right. Zip is always bringing things home for us to keep! I'll tell you about some of them. Zip's first present was a shoe. It was made of green silk. We didn't know how Zip found the shoe. But after a moment Mary, my big sister, told me the shoe had a strange smell. I nodded and held my nose. \"What do you think it is?\" \"It smells like something for cleaning. I think someone tried to clean a spot off the shoe. Then he put it at the door to dry.\" \"Along came Zip. And good-bye shoe!\" I said.\"We should take it back.\" \"We can't \".said my sistter. \"Maybe little Tom is right,\" Mary said. \"Maybe Zip is a keep dog!\"...\n\nQ: The word \"keep\" in the last sentence means \"  _  \"", "options": ["keeping things for itself", "bringing things for other to keep", "not letting it run about", "taking care of a small child"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3411, "question": "Friendly doctors are\"bad for their patients'health\",researchers have warned as a new study revealed two thirds of young doctors struggle to be truthful with patients they like. Blurring(...)the lines between social and professional relationships can affect the level of care offered and prevent patients from being honest about important side effects. \"Doctors should avoid adding patients as friends on Facebook,they should not hug or allow patients to call them by their first names\".regulators have warned.\"Those who break the boundaries will face some punishment.\" It comes as a survey of 338 oncologists under the age of 40,found 59 per cent said they found it difficult to tell the truth to those patients they liked.Sixty per cent of respondents said if doctors felt too close to their patient...\n\nQ: Young oncologists will face the following challenges except  _  .", "options": ["dealing with a lot of life-threatening diseases", "discussing difficulties of treatment with patients", "explaining the reason for the lack of some medicine", "informing patients of the possible results of the treatment"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2677, "question": "Science Fiction The science fiction type of entertainment is considered by most to be fathered by Jules Verne (A Journey to the Center of the Earth and Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea) and H. G. Wells (The Time Machine and The War of the Worlds). Sci-Fi, as it is commonly shortened, is a fictional story in which science and technology have a significant influence on the characters and plot. Many such works are guesswork about what the future holds and how scientific findings and technological advances will shape humankind. Writing in the late 1800s, Jules Verne was remarkably successful in his 10 guesses about future technologies of air conditioning, automobiles, the Internet, television, and underwater, air, and space travel. Unbelievably, of all places from which to choose, Jules V...\n\nQ: According to the author, what is the role of science fiction in society?", "options": ["A moral compass.", "A reference of technology.", "A record of science development.", "A consideration of possibilities."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1756, "question": "Having spent five years searching for her older brother, Miss Lund was unbelievable to think she had been working in the same building for five months. Mr.Philips, 33, and Miss Lund last saw each other almost twenty years ago after their father, also called Stephen, 56, lost contact with his son from a previous relationship.Miss Lund, only five at that time, moved to India with her father and mother Rose, while Steven lived with his mother in Wolverhapton. By the time Miss Lund and her parents returned to Leeds, the family had lost all contact with Mr.Philips.On turning 18, Lund started to track down her long-lost half brother, even asking customers at the shop where she worked.But despite checking on Internet sites such as Friends Reunited and MySpace, it wasn't until the pair started wor...\n\nQ: How old may Miss Lund be now?", "options": ["5", "18", "About 23", "About 27"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2675, "question": "Science Fiction The science fiction type of entertainment is considered by most to be fathered by Jules Verne (A Journey to the Center of the Earth and Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea) and H. G. Wells (The Time Machine and The War of the Worlds). Sci-Fi, as it is commonly shortened, is a fictional story in which science and technology have a significant influence on the characters and plot. Many such works are guesswork about what the future holds and how scientific findings and technological advances will shape humankind. Writing in the late 1800s, Jules Verne was remarkably successful in his 10 guesses about future technologies of air conditioning, automobiles, the Internet, television, and underwater, air, and space travel. Unbelievably, of all places from which to choose, Jules V...\n\nQ: Which of the following best summarizes the description of Nineteen Eighty-Four?", "options": ["A prediction of future technologies.", "A warning of cruel and unfair ruling.", "The consequence of scientific findings.", "An imaginary perfect world of freedom."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1358, "question": "When people get bad toothaches, they often have to eat soft, easily chewed food. When lions get bad toothaches, they eat people? That' s the conclusion of a zoologist at the Field Museum of Natural History in Chicago and a dentist who works on carnivores ., Lions don't normally prey on people. Every once in a while, however, a lion will go on a human-eating diet. The most famous such tragedy happened in 1898, when two lions killed and ate 135 railway workers in prefix = st1 /Kenya. Examining the preserved skulls of the two big cats, zoologist Bruce Patterson and dentist Ellis Neiburger found that both animals had been suffering from several dental and |aw problems. One lion had three missing teeth and a loose, unsteady lower canine that was probably useless. Canines are pointed teeth that ...\n\nQ: The best title of the passage could be   _  .", "options": ["A Zoologist And a Dentist", "Why Do Some Wild Animals Eat People", "A Discovery of the Skulls of Lions", "How Can Health Influence Eating Habits"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 879, "question": "A new international study shows that six people die every minute from smoking. That is 3 million deaths around the world every year. If the present rate of smoking continues, the number of deaths each year from smoking could rise to 10 million by the year 2020. The study describes smoking is the biggest cause of deadly diseases among grown-ups in industrial countries. So far most of the smoking deaths have happened to men, especially in developing countries. A researcher at the World Health Organization says 70% of Chinese men smoke more than 15 cigarettes each day. In Latin America about 50% of the men are smokers. There also are a very large number of smokers in Russia and in Eastern Europe. And 25% of all smoking deaths worldwide are in those areas of the world. Scientists say smoking w...\n\nQ: Which disease is not mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["heart attack", "lung cancer", "cancer of the mouth", "bronchitis"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2421, "question": "Recently I have discovered it's often easier for me to do something every day than to do it just some days. I post to my blog six days a week. I take notes every day. I write in my one-sentence journal every day. Many people have told me that they find it easier to exercise when they exercise every day. If I try to do something just four days a week, I spend a lot of time arguing with myself: Is today the day, or is it tomorrow, or the next day? Does the week start on Sunday or Monday? If you do something every day, you tend to fall into a routine. Routine has a bad reputation for lacking excitement. It's true that novelty and challenge bring happiness and that people who break their routines, try new things, and go to new places are happier, but I think that some routine activities also b...\n\nQ: Which can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["A Way To Form A Habit", "Do Anything Every Day", "Repeat Regularly", "Power Of Everyday Repetition"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2754, "question": "In summer, millions of people will head for the beach.And while the ocean can be a great place to swim and play, it may also be useful in another way.Some scientists think that waves could help make electricity. \"Have you ever been on a surfboard or boat and felt yourself being lifted up by a wave? Or have you jumped in the water and felt the energy as waves crashed over you?\" asked Jamie Taylor of the Wave Energy Group at the University of Edinburgh in Scotland.\"There is certainly a lot of energy in waves.\" Scientists are working on using that energy to make electricity. Most waves are created when winds blow across the ocean.\"The winds start out by making little ripples in the water, but if they keep on blowing , those ripples get bigger and bigger and turn into waves, \"Taylor said.\"Wave...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["finding new energy sources like wave energy is important", "wave energy is a resource that will never run out and is used all over the world", "wave power is perfect for creating energy around the world", "wave power doesn't create any pollution."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1499, "question": "First Lady Michelle Obama is a big fan of volunteering. Volunteering means working for free to help someone else. Mrs. Obama says volunteering is very important. \"It should be part of everyone's life, \" she says. Many teens agree. They say that helping others feels great and makes a difference. These days, more teens volunteer than work for pay. Teens clean up parks, walk dogs at animal shelters , visit the elderly and more. Some cities ---- including Seatle, Chicago, and Washingtong,D.C. ----require high school students to volunteer. Students must volunteer in order to graduate. The student volunteers learn new skills and help theircommunities . Many parents _ the idea ---- they say volunteering helps teens build job skills. But most teens don't want to be forced to volunteer. They say th...\n\nQ: The writer mentions Michelle Obama in order to  _  ,", "options": ["introduce the topic of the text", "explain what volunteering is", "tell what she does for the US", "show she enjoys volunteering"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 979, "question": "Schouten University is a highly respected online education provider offering officially-recognized degree programs across the globe. Our mission is to provide students with a high-quality mixed learning MBA program and personal coaching to help them to become world-class managers. MBA with Unique Skills & Personal Development Program Students will benefit from 30 years of soft skills training experience from Schouten & Nielsen, the leading soft skills training institute in Europe. To become an effective manager, theory alone is not enough, and being able to put theory into practice is more important today than ever before. With the Schouten University MBA program you will have the unique opportunity to develop such soft skills as influencing skills, leadership skills, communication skills ...\n\nQ: The advertisement is probably intended for   _  .", "options": ["full-time college students", "working businessmen", "studying teenagers", "retired managers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1011, "question": "After the first World War, a small group of veterans returned to their village in Britain. Most of them managed to get along fairly well, but one--Francis Blustering, who had been wounded and who never recovered his strength-- was unable to work like others. In time he became very poor. Yet he was too proud to accept anything from the people in the village. Once, these veterans held a reunion dinner in the home of Jules Grandin, who had made a good deal of money. Grandin produced a curiosity --a large old gold coin. Each man examined it with interest as it passed around the long table. All, however, had drunk wine freely and the room was full of noisy talk, so that the gold piece was soon forgotten. Later, when Grandin remembered it and asked for it, the coin was missing. One of them sugge...\n\nQ: When Blustering turned red and refused to be searched, all people thought   _  .", "options": ["he was really a poor fellow", "he must have stolen the gold coin", "the coin must be hidden somewhere in the room", "poor Blustering had hidden some food in his pockets"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3178, "question": "NOT all math skills are learned in the classroom. Some of them come naturally. Consider the split-second calculations you make when you estimate the number of empty seats on the school bus or the number of cookies in a cookie jar. These estimates can often be done without counting. That's because humans are born with the ability to closely guess the number of items in a group. Researchers call this ability a person's \"number sense\". To see how a person's inborn number sense might be linked to mathematical performance in the classroom, psychologist Justin Halberda and his colleagues from Johns Hopkins University in prefix = st1 /Baltimore,USran some tests. The scientists asked 64 14-year-olds to look at images of yellow and blue dots that flashed on a computer screen for a fraction of a sec...\n\nQ: Justin Halberda and his colleagues ran some tests to_.", "options": ["look at the students' math scores dating back to kindergarten.", "ask the students to estimate the dots", "see if a person's inborn number sense has something to do with math learning", "decide how to learn math well"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1941, "question": "Mary went out at night. She never forgot the night when she met a robber many years ago. That evening, she was invited to a birthday party which lasted until two o'clock in the morning. Without company Mary walked along the quiet street. Suddenly from the shadow of a dark building a tall man with a sharp knife in his right hand ran out at her. \"Good evening, lady,\" the man said in a low voice, \"I don't think you wish to die here.\" \"What do you want?\" Mary asked. \"Your earrings .Take them off!\" Slowly Mary's eyes looked down. She tried to cover her necklace with the collar of her overcoat while she used the other hand to take off both of her earrings, and then she quickly threw them on the ground. \"Take them and let me go.\" she said. The robber looked at her only feeling uncertain. He saw t...\n\nQ: The story tells us that she was a   _  girl.", "options": ["clever and brave", "clever and beautiful", "brave and careful", "clever and careful"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2245, "question": "Drownings, bicycle injuries, falls, and pedestrian accidents are the most common causes of childhood injury or death. Here's what you need to know to avoid tragedy: * Drowning: Each year, thousands of children die from drowning, with two-thirds of accidents occurring in the summer. To protect kids, parents should install multiple layers of protective devices, with each layer offering another opportunity to avoid a tragedy. Fences, door alarms, pool covers are all somewhat effective individually, but their effectiveness is increased dramatically when used in combination with one another. * Falls: Falls from heights kill 140 children under the age of 15 each year in the United States, and seriously injure three million more, making falls the leading cause of non-deadly injury for this age gr...\n\nQ: When riding a bicycle, you should   _   according to the AAP.", "options": ["avoid riding at night", "not take anyone in the back seat", "wear a proper helmet", "not ride on the streets under the age of 14"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2316, "question": "Unemployment in Europe has recently hit record highs. Although Denmark has been protected from economic problems thanks to its low public debt, qualified professionals are still finding it tough to get a job. Danish marketing firm Reputation Copenhagen has come up with a way of helping academics get noticed -- putting them on display in storefront windows. Many highly-trained professionals, ranging from former CEOs to lawyers and tax experts, are currently finding it increasingly difficult to find proper employment on the Danish job market. Some of them have been trying for years, leaving their resumes with dozens of companies, without ever hearing back from them, and are now at a point where they are willing to try anything, even putting themselves in display windows like goods, hoping to...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["Job-seekers are displayed in the windows hoping to get hired.", "The rate of unemployment in Europe has recently become hitter.", "It is hard for qualified professionals to get a job.", "Denmark has avoided economic problems due to its low public debt."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3369, "question": "My dad is a wonderful man.He worked hard all his life and has never let me down.if one person influenced me to go to college and become a better person, it's him. Every morning my dad would wake up at 4 am.He would do some writing and then Ieave for work.He would get off work at 5 pm and spend the remaining day with his family.Any time I needed him,he was there.He was a great role model.My dad is a typical family man.He supports us financially and emotionally.He bends over backward to support his family. My dad is the reason why I try to support my son as much as I can.He is also the reason why I have decided to spend less time with friends and more time with family.Now I'm a much better woman.I once worked hard at my studies in school and now do well in my work.My dad became a manager in ...\n\nQ: With the example of two raises,the author shows us that   _   .", "options": ["she worked very hard in her company", "she spent less time with her son", "she has a talent for leadership", "she can be a good psychologist."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 60, "question": "Nelson Mandela was a figure of international fame, and many details of his life and career were public knowledge. But here are four things you may not have known about the late South African leader. 1. He was a boxing fan. In his youth, Nelson Mandela enjoyed boxing and long-distance running. Even during the 27 years he spent in prison, he would exercise every morning. \"I did not enjoy the violence of boxing so much as the science of it. I was curious by how one moved one's body to protect oneself, how one used a strategy both to attack and retreat, how one paced oneself over a match,\" he wrote in his autobiography Long Walk to Freedom. 2. His original name was not Nelson. Rolihlahla Mandela was nine years old when a teacher at the primary Methodist school where he was studying in Qunu, So...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Nelson Mandela's life in the prison.", "The achievements of Nelson Mandela.", "Nelson Mandela's hobbies and career.", "Unknown things about Nelson Mandela."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 55, "question": "A desert is a beautiful land of silence and space. The sun shines, the wind blows, and time and space seem endless. Nothing is soft. The sand and rocks are hard, and many of the plants even have hard needles instead of leaves. The size and location of the world's deserts are always changing. Over millions of years, as climates change and mountains rise, new dry and wet areas develop. But within the last 100 yeas, deserts have been growing at a frightening speed. This is partly because of natural changes, but the greatest makers are humans. Humans can make deserts, but humans can also prevent their growth. Algeria Mauritania is planting a similar wall around Nouakchott, the capital. Iran puts a thin covering of petroleum on sandy areas and plants trees. The oil keeps the water and small tre...\n\nQ: In this passage, \"needles\" refers to   _  .", "options": ["small, thin pieces of steel.", "long, thin pieces of branches.", "small pointed growth on the stem of a plant.", "small, thin pieces of sticks."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1865, "question": "My father always told me never to ever reveal my true opinions towards other people unless such opinions are positive. He said this is the \"Chu Shi Zhe Xue\", the philosophy of dealing with social network. It seems that everybody here just follows this philosophy very, very well. I would say that if I were given true friendship I would definitely treasure it with my greatest care. If I really regard someone as my close friend, I would never leave her alone whenever she's in need, either financially or mentally. And I always believe, as long as I treat people with whole-hearted honesty, I would have some rewards--at least, just ONE true friend of the same gender. Sometimes I just miss my friends in China. Perhaps when we became friends, we were still young, too young to have been polluted by...\n\nQ: Why does the writer mention the song twice in the passage?", "options": ["She likes the song very much.", "The singer is one of her friends.", "The song expresses her feelings.", "She uses it to perfects her article."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2659, "question": "Along a long path we came to a deep valley, on the far side of which the path led into some very thick bushes. Rather than push through up again and rejoin the path on the far side of the bushes As I climbed down into the valley a bird flew off h rock on which I had put my hand. On looking at the spot from which the bird had risen, I saw two eggs. They were the kind that I did not have in my collection, so I placed them carefully in my bag, wrapped in a little dry grass. As we went further down the valley the sides became steeper and not far from where I had entered. It came to drop of about twelve to fourteen feet. The water that rushed down all these small valleys in the rainy season had worn the rock as glass. As it was too deep to climb down, I handed my gun to one of the men and slid ...\n\nQ: When the writer found the eggs, he   _  .", "options": ["wrapped them in dry grass and put them aside", "wrapped them in dry grass and took them with him", "tried to find the bird", "made the bird fly off"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1841, "question": "One rainy night , Mark decided to end his life . Having undergone a lot of sufferings and frustrations , he walked the streets , feeling desperate . On that same night , I was sitting in my room when I heard the doorbell rang . My mom opened the door , finding herself face-to-face with a very disheveled-looking man , Mark , with tears running down his face . My mom , overcome by pity , invited him inside . Curious , I went downstairs to get a better look . The sight of the man , holding his head in his hands and crying , made my chest ache . I raced back upstairs to my room , pulled out my only half-dollar coin from my money jar and ran back downstairs . When I reached the door of the living room , I walked right in and quickly made my way over to the stranger . I put the half-dollar in hi...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best describe the author ?", "options": ["Curious and desperate.", "Sympathetic and nice.", "Miserable and kind.", "Brave and thoughtful."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2994, "question": "Almost 70 percent of Chinese middle school students have serious problems with their parents, the Beijing Morning Post quoted a survey as saying. The survey showed 6.62 percent of the surveyed students are afraid of their parents while 13.13 percent of them dislike their parents and 56.28 percent were extremely disgusted with or even hate their parents. Only 4.75 percent of the young people surveyed said they like their parents. The recently conducted survey among 3,000 middle school students in a Beijing district asked questions about their attitude toward their parents and family education, the paper said. For many families, conflict between parents and children center on the student's school grades, their weight and their friends. The survey showed that parental influence over children ...\n\nQ: Xiao Xiao is mentioned as an example to show that   _   .", "options": ["parental influence over children is decreasing.", "one should study hard to attend Beijing University as a student.", "Parents today expect too high from their children.", "today's children spend too much time surfing the web."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1847, "question": "Table manners are very different in every country. For example, when you are in England you must not lift your soup plate to your mouth. This is very impolite. But when you are in Japan this is completely normal. Lifting your plate to your mouth in Japan is a traditional way of drinking your soup. And also in Japan you don't have to worry about making a noise when you drink it. It just shows that you really like the food! But it is not the same in Britain, so you shouldn't make a noise when eating there. In Britain, people don't put their hands or arms on the table during the meal. But in Mexico, guests keep their hands on the table all the time. In fact, you should watch what your hands do very carefully. In Arab countries, it is impolite when you eat with your left hand, so don't do it! ...\n\nQ: When you are ea ting in Japan, making a noise means that   _  .", "options": ["you feel ill", "you dislike the fo od", "you like the food", "you are very hungry"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3223, "question": "\"For those who haven't been to Tibet is a dream; for those who have already been there, Tibet is a memory.\" said Li Wan, a graduate from Zhongshan University. \"For me, living there is my dream and happiness.\" Li was suddenly crazy about Tibet after working there for three months as an office clerk. Since 2008, Li has spent most of her time travelling in Tibet. Four years have passed and she has been almost every corner of Tibet. Li came to Tibet firstly because of her desire for personal freedom. She entered Tibet along the Yunnan-Tibetan road, enjoying the special view happily. She was surprised to find that it is a white paradise on earth. Although she couldn't even speak a word of Tibetan language, she had no difficulty in communicating with natives. \"To me, they are free, generous, sim...\n\nQ: This passage mainly talks about   _  .", "options": ["the challenges Li Wan met in Tibet", "the travel of Li Wan made in Tibet", "the people Li Wan communicated with in Tibet", "the route of Li Wan planned in Tibet"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1316, "question": "The Isle of Wight, off the south coast of England, is the best place in Europe for discovering dinosaur bones. Dinosaur Farm Museum was established in 1993. Since then, the museum has introduced the study of old bones to many more people. What we offer Visitors can enjoy our displays, or watch us cleaning dinosaur bones and other fossils found on the island's beaches. The museum has a variety of different fossils, many of them never displayed to the public before. As more are discovered all the time, you can be sure of seeing something new each time you visit. We have a free Fossil Identification Service, so you can bring in any fossils you have and find out what they are. In addition, we have a reasonably-priced Museum Shop, where you can buy a souvenir of your visit. You could also bring...\n\nQ: One can book a fossil hunt   _  .", "options": ["through a BBC programme", "through the museum's website", "by making a call to the museum", "by visiting the museum personally"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1130, "question": "We are not rich by what we possess but rather by what we can do without. ----Immauel Kant Many times my friend June would say, \"If I ever get rich, I'm getting a completely new wardrobe and moving into a bigger apartment.\" I thought of her words and her chances of being rich are about as good as mine. But, to everyone's surprise, a few years ago June did come to large inheritance . At first June said very little about the money. As the initial shock disappeared, she became excited, June is a great believer in making lists, so I was surprised to find her writing down all the ways she would spend her new wealth. As time went on, she started revising the list. What had been midway down the list was now at the top. At last, I said to her, \"You know, it isn't necessary to spend all your inherit...\n\nQ: From the passage we can learn that the writer at first  _  .", "options": ["was richer than her friend June", "was no richer than her friend June", "was poorer than her friend June", "was interested in money as June"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 890, "question": "If you're one of the 13 million Americans still struggling to find a job, or wanting to change jobs, a lot of your applications are probably being swallowed up by the \"the black hole.\" That's when you send in a job application and never receive any follow-up from the company.In fact, only 25 out of 100 applications ever get looked at by companies. Now, a remarkable new service is helping job seekers instantly track almost every application they submit so they actually know what's going on.It's called Start Wire. corn and it lets job seekers track their applications and find out whether or not their applications have been reviewed, dismissed, or are still being considered. How does it work? When you fill out a job application via a company website, you'll typically get an auto confirmation ...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly intended to  _", "options": ["prove the advantages of Start Wire", "attract more people to use Start Wire", "teach people how to access Start Wire", "provide key facts about unemployment"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2275, "question": "I have a painfully vivid memory of my first homecoming from college, in December 1983. After three whole months away, I was back home with my brand new opinions, attitudes and tastes. How could they watch such terrible television programs? I, the English Literature major with Shakespeare and Milton and James Joyce, could hardly bear to sleep under the roof of a house whose few bookshelves held thrillers and bound editions of the Reader's Digest. I'm sure my family was glad to see the back of me when, at the end of the holiday, I packed up my books and headed back up to university in the north of England. But the next year must have been even more painful to my parents: I didn't show up at all. Now, I don't think there's anything wrong with young people spending a little time away from thei...\n\nQ: If you are a person who is wet behind the ears, you are  _  .", "options": ["old and experienced", "young and inexperienced", "young and experienced", "mature and experienced"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 77, "question": "What's your idea of a good time? What about dancing in a rainy field with one hundred and fifty thousand other people while a famous rock band plays on a stage so far away that the performers look like ants? It may sound strange but that is what many hundreds of thousands of young people in the UK do every summer.Why? Because summer is the time for outdoor music festivals. Held on a farm, the Glastonbury Festival is the most well-known and popular festival in the UK.It began in 1970 and the first festival was attended by one thousand five hundred people each paying an admission price of PS1 -- the ticket included free milk from the farm. Since then the Glastonbury Festival has gone from strength to strength -- in 2004 one hundred and fifty thousand fans attended, paying PS112 each for a ti...\n\nQ: What does the author mean by saying \"the Glastonbury Festival has gone from strength to strength\"?", "options": ["The festival has achieved growing success.", "Great efforts have been made to hold the festival.", "The festival has brought in a large amount of money.", "There have been thousands of fans attending the festival."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3409, "question": "Friendly doctors are\"bad for their patients'health\",researchers have warned as a new study revealed two thirds of young doctors struggle to be truthful with patients they like. Blurring(...)the lines between social and professional relationships can affect the level of care offered and prevent patients from being honest about important side effects. \"Doctors should avoid adding patients as friends on Facebook,they should not hug or allow patients to call them by their first names\".regulators have warned.\"Those who break the boundaries will face some punishment.\" It comes as a survey of 338 oncologists under the age of 40,found 59 per cent said they found it difficult to tell the truth to those patients they liked.Sixty per cent of respondents said if doctors felt too close to their patient...\n\nQ: What should doctors do according to the regulations?", "options": ["Add patients as friends on Facebook.", "Have close connection with patients in life.", "Always be cold to patients.", "Keep a proper distance to patients."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2646, "question": "Are you a creative person? Are you looking for a challenging and unique work environment? Picture yourself at CRIENGLISH.com Positions open to native English Speakers Only Video reporters/editors: 1. Video editing experience with an understanding of Final Cut Pro software. 2. Resourceful and creative when it comes to finding original stories. 3. A comfortable demeanor in front of the camera. 4. Enjoy working with others in a team oriented environment. News presenters: 1. Journalistic and radio experience, good news-writing skills. 2. Able to work the night and early morning shifts. 3. Team spirit and flexibility. Biz News Reporter/Presenter: 1. Journalistic experience, particularly in the field of business news. 2. Good reading and presentation skills. 3. Able to work at irregular hours. C...\n\nQ: To apply for the positions above, one must  _  .", "options": ["work long hours", "have related working experience", "have team spirit", "live in English-speaking countries"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1170, "question": "Computer power is moving into the \"cloud\"--networks of data centres that use the Internet to supply all kinds of services, from e-mail and social networks to data storage and analysis. The rise of cloud computing is rapid and causing huge changes in the tech industry. The old guard is suffering: this week's $67 billion merger between Dell and EMC, makers of computers and storage devices respectively , was a marriage forced by the rise of the cloud. Disruptive newcomers are blooming: if Amazon's cloud-computing unit were a stand-alone public company, it would probably be worth almost as much as Dell and EMC combined. The gains for customers have been equally dramatic. Compared with older IT systems, cloud computing is often much cheaper. It adds tremendous flexibility: firms that need more ...\n\nQ: The author takes \"the merger between Dell and EMC\" for example to show   _  .", "options": ["the influence of cloud computing on computer and storage device makers", "the miserable sufferings of old computer companies", "the rapid development of new computer companies", "the interaction between old companies and newcomers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3432, "question": "The small coastal town of Broome, in northwest Australia, is a remote village in the vast countryside. There are no traffic jams and hardly any roads. There is only the massive Australian wild land, where some houses are 500 miles apart and some driveways are 50 miles long. There seem to be only two main sources of entertainment out here: the sunset at the beach and Sun Pictures. Sun Pictures is a very different movie theater:The seats are park benches and deck chairs, but you're also welcome to sit on the grass. It is the world's oldest outdoor movie garden. Sun Pictures was built in 1916 on the other side of the globe from Hollywood. All the big films were shipped here and the lonely country was amazed. Broome resident Pearl Hamaguchi has never traveled far from home. But in the Sun Pict...\n\nQ: . Gregory Peck is most probably the name of  _  .", "options": ["a place", "a film", "a movie star", "a country fellow"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1435, "question": "Life is full of sweet surprises for Chinese pop singer Edell. She majored in design in a Canadian college. But when she was looking for a job after graduation, she found herself rising as a star in singing. Then she became a hostess on TV. \"These are roles I never expected to take,\" she said. Edell is open to every possibility in life, not afraid to try new things. She says that every day she tries to get herself ready to take any chance that occurs in life. \"My mom told me chance only rewards those with a prepared mind,\" she said. \"So I've tried to explore my potential talents. Thus I won't be at a loss when the right opportunity comes up.\" Edell learned ballet in her childhood until she broke her back in practice. She then fell in love with music. Like many girls of her age, she has a ri...\n\nQ: The writer mentioned Edell's mother to tell us  _  .", "options": ["her chances were given by her mother", "her mother had great influence on her", "she could do nothing without her mother", "all her success belonged to her mother"], "answer": 1}]